http://www.caselogic.com/en/about-case-logic/privacy-statement

Skip to main content
Search
Search text
Search result on
Total :
Go to caselogic start page
LIFE, SIMPLIFIED.
Legal and Privacy Policy
Case Logic takes user privacy seriously; we believe people should be able to contact us without fear of being tracked or overloaded with SPAM. Because we understand how important it is that you know what will happen to any personal information you give us, our mission is to adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use of your personal information, to maintain the accuracy of the information provided, and to protect the privacy of your information. We have created this policy to explain how we collect data on our website, and to educate users about what we do with this data.
What information does Case Logic collect and how is it used?
E-mail Request for Information - We use links throughout our site so that you can contact us via e-mail to ask questions, request information and materials or send comments and suggestions. We may also ask to have one of our representatives contact you personally to provide additional information about our products or services. In this case, we may request additional personal information from you, such as your name and telephone number, to help us satisfy your request.
Enrollment - If you choose to signup for our e-newsletter and special offers, we will request certain information from you. You may be asked to provide personal details, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or credit card number. Other promotions may require different or supplemental information from you in order to apply.
In addition to the information we get directly from you, we also gather information such as general usage of our website, viewing and traffic patterns, customer behavior and other similar information that is not specific to any one person. We use this compiled information solely for the improvement of our website, our product and service offerings, our operations, and our customer service.
Does Case Logic disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
No! Case Logic does not resell any confidential customer information that is obtained or derived in its marketing efforts. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.
Why do you need my e-mail address?
We may contact you by e-mail to confirm enrollment, check the accuracy of supplied information or send you notices about special offers, new products, services, promotions and other similar information. If you don’t want to receive e-mails from us, please advise us by e-mail. We will respect your wishes regarding the methods we use to communicate with you.
What are cookies?
"Cookies" are helpful pieces of information about you that a website stores on your hard disk to make your return visits to the website more convenient. For example, Case Logic uses cookies to help identify you so that you can access your member benefits quickly and easily. We do not use cookies to collect personal information or to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the website or your interaction with the website.
Do these same policies apply to non- Case Logic websites that I access through Case Logic?
We cannot be responsible for the privacy and security practices of non- Case Logic websites. You will notice that our websites may contain links to other sites such as our benefit providers. While we believe these sites share a similar commitment to consumer privacy and security, you should review that site’s privacy and security policies when linking to their site.
How does Case Logic update its Privacy and Security Policy?
Any changes to our Privacy and Security Policy will be posted on this page so that you always know what information we collect and how we use it and the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our websites. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information as it is disclosed in this Privacy and Security Policy Statement.
Trademark and copyright
A trademark is a word, logotype, slogan, colour or shape that identifies and distinguishes the source or origin of a product or service. All trademarks belonging to Thule Group are important and valuable assets of the company.
The Thule Group respects the Intellectual Property rights of others, and we ask the same of others.
Unless otherwise indicated on this site, all trademarks, brand names and corporate logos are the property of Thule Group or its affiliates and protected by Intellectual Property Rights Law.
Trademarks, brand names and corporate logos belonging to Thule Group may not be used in any way without the prior written permission from Thule Group.
The copyright of this website, including without limitation, all documents, files, text, images, graphics, devices, sound, audio-visual elements, is owned by Thule Group and is protected by Swedish and international copyright laws. (All Rights Reserved)
The website or any part of it may not, apart from what is stated below, be reproduced, duplicated, copied, transferred, distributed, stored or otherwise exploited for any commercial use without prior written permission by Thule Group. No links to this website may be included in any other website without the prior written permission by Thule Group. Modifications to the contents on this website are expressly prohibited.
You are authorized to view, print and copy any document published on this website for your personal non-commercial use and provided that any such copy or print retains all copyright or other proprietary notices.
You are authorized to use information from this website if it is only used for information purposes, provided the source of information is mentioned. You may copy and print press releases and other documents classified as public.
The content of the information may not be modified and the information should be used in a way that does not harm the reputation of Thule Group.
The website may contain images that are subject to copyright of third parties.
